（纽约市 联合国）
（英国）
由联合国秘书长
Was so ably pointed out by the secretary general…
在揭幕演说中提出
…in his opening remarks.
可是…我必须强调
But… and I must emphasize this point…
没有公式能涵盖所有案例
…no formula can or will ever cover each case.
举例来说…
For instance…
当有三个或更多申请人被认可
When three or more applicants have been recognized…
这就会直接引起冲突…
…which is in direct contradiction to…
（新奥尔良 路易斯安那）
（灵魂之最）
谁的丧礼？
Whose funeral is it?
你的
Yours.
（加勒比海的圣莫尼克岛）
《007系列之生死关头》
再来一次吗？
One more time again?
大概你还没结婚吧？
You're not married by any chance, are you?
你早 007
Good morning, 007.
早
Good morning.
先生 失眠了吗？
Insomnia, sir?
下指示了
Instructions.
你的时间不多了 我一面解释 你一面整理行李
You haven't much time. I'll explain as you pack.
整理什么行李 长官？
Pack, sir?
过去24小时 我们有三位干员被杀
Three of our agents were killed during the last 24 hours:
纽约的桃尔 新奥尔良的汉米顿…
Dawes in New York, HamiIton in New Orleans…
加勒比海的班恩
…and Baines in the Caribbean.
班恩 我蛮喜欢班恩 我们去同一家鞋店
Baines. I rather liked Baines. We shared the same boot maker.
喝咖啡吗？
Coffee?
先生？
Sir?
我认为这些谋杀案互有关连
I take it these killings are connected.
就是要你查个水落石出
That's precisely what you're going to find out.
班恩在加勒比海圣莫尼克的小岛工作
Baines was working on a small island in the Caribbean called San Monique.
桃尔在纽约
Dawes was in New York…
一边监视它的首相：康乃克博士
…keeping an eye on its prime minister, one Dr. kananga.
汉米被美国人借到新奥尔良
HamiIton was on loan to the Americans in New Orleans.
它的功用就这样吗？
Is that all it does?
对了 我应该要恭喜你才对
By the way, congratulations seem to be in order.
意大利人对你处理罗马事件印象深刻
The Italians were most impressed by the way you handled the Rome affair.
谢谢 先生 要加糖吗？
Thank you, sir. Sugar?
谢谢
Thanks.
当地官员可帮了大忙
The authorities were more than helpful.
只有一点美中不足
There's one small complaint.
他们似乎有一名干员失踪了
They seem to be missing one of their agents…
是个小姐 嗯 叫可鲁索
…a Miss Caruso.
你大概不知道她在哪吧？
You wouldn't happen to know where she is?
啊 钱班霓小姐
Ah, Miss Moneypenny.
早上好 钱班霓
Good morning, Moneypenny.
- 你好 先生 - 来的时间真是不巧
- Good morning, sir. - Certainly the hour that's indecent.
真的吗？我这有你去纽约的机票
Really? I've got your ticket to New York.
Q也修好你的手表
Q has repaired your wristwatch.
还有一些圣莫尼克的背景资料
And some background material on San Monique.
谢谢你 钱班霓
Thank you, Moneypenny.
我相信负担沉重的英国纳税人 一定好奇地要知道…
I'm sure the overburdened British taxpayer will be fascinated to know…
特别处理小组如何运用它的基金
…how the Special Ordnance Section disburses its funds.
以后 队长我建议你…
ln future, Commander, allow me to suggest…
街上不远就有个很棒的钟表匠
…a perfectly adequate watchmaker just down the street.
老天爷
Good God.
先生 把这个按钮拉出来
By pulling out this button, sir…
这表就产生强力电磁场
…it turns the watch into a hyperintensified magnetic field…
力量强到能让一颗子弹转向
…powerful enough to even deflect the path of a bullet…
Q说至少长射程是这样
…at long range, or so Q claims.
我真想现在就试试这个理论
I feel very tempted to test that theory right now.
队长 若你不介意 请还我汤匙
If you don't mind, Commander, my spoon.
哦 抱歉 先生
Oh, sorry, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
康乃克博士目前在纽约
Dr. kananga is, at present, in New York.
已经通知中情局 他们答应协助监视
The ClA have been informed, and they're helping with the surveillance.
你的班机上午11点30分到达
Your flight arrives at 11:30 a.m.
我把外套放到哪去了？
Now, where did I leave my coat?
哦 让我来吧
Oh, allow me.
谢谢 钱班霓 一起走吧
Thank you. Come along, Miss Moneypenny.
- 再见 邦德长官 - 再见 钱班霓小姐
- Good morning, Bond. - Sir. Miss Moneypenny.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见 詹姆斯
Good-bye, James.
或者我该说…
Or should I say…
「再见 朋友」？
… "Ciao, bello?"
如此优雅的触摸
Such a delicate touch.
纯粹是磁性 亲爱的
Sheer magnetism, darling.
有个男人来了
A man comes.
他速度很快
He traveIs quickly.
有备而来
He has purpose.
他跨洋越海
He comes over water.
跟其他人一起旅行
He traveIs with others.
他会抗争
He will oppose.
他带来暴力与毁灭
He brings violence and destruction.
嗨 莱特先生找你
Hello. Mr. Leiter for you, sir.
谢谢你 菲力 你好吗？
Thank you. Hello, Felix. How are you?
不塞车的话 我半小时就能到你那边
Traffic permitting, I should be with you in about haIf an hour.
到时 你就能请我吃纽约最好的午餐了
Then you can buy me the best lunch in New York.
好啊 詹姆斯 你朋友康乃克刚离开联合国
Fine, James. Your friend kananga has just left the U.N.
他可能回使馆去了
He's probably headed back to his embassy.
别担心 那地方已经受到严密监控
No, don't worry. I've got the place eyeballed, wired for sound, the works.
好吧 半小时后见
Right. I'll see you in a haIf hour.
开慢点 查理 要安全到达
Easy, Charlie. Let's get there in one piece.
查理？
Charlie?
好了 一切就绪
Right. Stand by.
康乃克的轿车来了
Here comes kananga's limousine.
他出来了…
Out he gets…
带著以前的班底…
…with the usual goon squad…
还有那个女孩
…and the girl.
时间 11点46分
Time, 11:46.
那是什么？
What is that?
嗨 菲力？你知道我多不喜欢麻烦你
Hello, Felix? You know how I hate to trouble you…
但我碰到点小困难
…but I've run into a little bother.
你的司机死了
Your driver is dead.
你说什么？
You what?
帮我追查一辆白色大轿车
Get me a make on a white pimpmobile.
347NDG的牌照
347 NeIson-David-George.
康乃克博士 看来这次会议还没…
It would seem, Dr. Kananga, that the conference has not lived up…
达到你事前的期望
…to your prior expectations.
我们希望这仅仅是短暂的挫败
We can only hope that this is a temporary setback.
不过 我还要观察一阵子
However, I do have some observations to make.
麻烦你写封信
Take a letter, please.
给岛屿协商潘秘书长
To Secretary General, Pan Island Unity Conference.
先生
Sir…
我希望
…I wish to point out…
指出
…that…
我们太多的邻国
…too many of our island neighbors…
再一次受到
…have once again let themselves be…
美国工业愚弄
…bullied by United States industry.
历史是老的
The story is an old one…
记录是明确的
…the record a clear one.
自从六个月前
Since my historic statement of principles…
执行了我历史性的宣告
…was delivered and acted upon some six months ago…
我们的经济展望 有很戏剧性的改善
…our economic outlook has improved dramatically.
在运用了我们一贯公平对待的友善政策后
By exercising our policy of friendship to all with favoritism towards none…
整个地区有了新的面貌
…new respect for the entire area has been engendered…
虽然我一些…
…and even though some of my most…
詹姆斯 车主登记住址在 38街和65街交界的一家店
James, that car is registered to a shop at 33 East 65th Street.
离这里只有一个街口 对
That's only a block away from here. Right.
谢谢你 老兄 康乃克在那里高谈阔论
Take your time, buddy. kananga's knitting a flag in there.
也许最简单的方法…
It might be the easiest thing to do…
（异教邪术商店）
需要什么吗？
Something in heads?
随便看看 谢谢
Just browsing. Thank you.
五圆
Five dollars.
帮我包起来好吗？
Do you think you could gift-wrap it for me, please?
如果你不介意 整个包起来
Lengthwise, if you don't mind.
谢谢
Thank you.
仍是我主要关心的事
Remains my first concern.
因此 圣莫尼克岛和其邻近岛国未来责任
Thus, San Monique's future obligations vis-a-vis her island neighbors…
就是非常明显了
…would seem clear.
在激怒时求饶的国家…
Those who fawn and crawl in the face of intimidation…
应该被强迫向那些有极度的信心而且…
…must perforce to look up to those who stand proudly…
屹立不摇的国家看齐
…wrapped in a justifiable seIf-confidence.
时机已到…
The time has come…
从联盟国家中
…painful as it may be…
虽然很痛苦
…to gaze out among our sister nations in the area…
若有任何…
…and see if any…
他在跟踪
He's tailing.
我看到他了
I got him in my sights.
- 你要上哪去？- 市中心
- Hey, you know where you going, man? - Uptown, I believe.
市中心？你要去哈林区
Uptown? You headed into Harlem, man.
你只要跟紧那部车 我多给你20元
Just keep on the tail of that jukebox and there's an extra 20 in it for you.
为了20元
Hey, man, for 20 bucks…
我愿意带你去3K党的老窝
…I'll take you to a klu klux klan cookout.
125号车 有辆车跟踪你
125th, you got a honky on your tail.
他向东驶去
He's heading east.
不会追丢 好像跟踪棒球
Can't miss him. It's like following a cue ball.
就是那辆车 他们一定进去了
That's the car. They must have gone inside.
靠边停
Pull up where you can.
希望你能很容易就交到些朋友
Sure hope you make friends easy.
谢谢 兄弟！
Right on, brother!
他要走进去了
He's heading on in.
午安 我要波本酒加水
Good afternoon. Bourbon and water, please.
第一个位子就行了
First booth will do.
- 告诉他不加冰块 好吗？- 什么？
- Tell him neat, would you? - Huh?
- 不要冰块 - 那要多加钱的
- No ice. - That's extra, man.
我要其他一些消息
I'd like something on the side as well information.
三男一女刚走进来
Three men and a girl came in.
放轻松点 宝贝
Relax, baby.
老大等下会招呼你
Mr. Big's gonna take care of you in a minute.
黑桃皇后在红心国王旁边 小姐是…
Black queen on the red king, Miss…
- 沙丽塔 - 我叫邦德
- Solitaire. - My name's Bond.
詹姆斯邦德
James Bond.
我知道你是谁 你的身份和来此的原因
I know who you are, what you are and why you've come.
你犯了个错误 你不会成功的
You have made a mistake. You will not succeed.
在我们素昧平生的情况下 这说法令人感动
Rather a sweeping statement, considering we've never met.
纸牌替我跟踪你
The cards have followed you for me.
若你在底特律遭遇困难 你就说我的名字 知道吗？
Now, you get ripped off in Detroit, baby, you yell out to me, you hear?
他有带武器吗？
Is he armed?
在纽约市你不能不特别小心
You can't be too careful in New York City these days.
奇怪 这点小事声使他发笑
Funny how the least little thing amuses him.
真迷人
Oh, fascinating.
很显然的 这张是你
That's you, quite obviously.
高级女祭司 简直一模一样
An amazing resemblance.
告诉我 我也在里面吗？
Tell me, am I in there as well?
选一张牌
Pick a card.
翻过去
Turn it over.
（傻瓜）
你找到你自己了
You have found yourseIf.
我告诉你 你去洛杉矶处理
I'm telling you, y'all go out there to L.A. and clean it up…
否则我会去处理你！我说真的
…or I'm coming out there and clean you up, and I mean that!
就是这个笨家伙跟踪你进城吗？
Is this the stupid mother that tailed you uptown?
这似乎有点误会 我叫…
There seems to be some mistake. My name is…
把名字留给墓碑吧
Names is for tombstones, baby.
你带家伙出去 把他做了
Y'all take this honky out and waste him, now.
- 「做掉他」？这是好事吗？- 会面结束
- "Waste him"? Is that a good thing? - The reading is over.
没谈我的将来？
Nothing about my future?
（情侣）
我们？
Us?
答应我待在这里 我马上回来
Now, promise you'll stay right there. I shan't be long.
谢谢
Thank you.
手举起来
keep your hands up, honky.
他以为这是什么？我要把他头轰掉
What does he think this is? I'll blow his head off, man.
枪放下！
Drop it!
现在！
Now.
哈洛史特劳 中情局 我不需要你时 你在哪？
Harold Strutter, ClA. Where were you when I didn't need you?
显然你不了解情况
Got obvious you weren't coming out front…
就像你穿的衣服 也不是个聪明的伪装
…not even with that clever disguise you're wearing.
- 什么？- 哈林区白面孔
- Er? - Whiteface in Harlem.
好主意 邦德 我们离开这
Good thinking, Bond. Let's get out of here.
我很惊讶 他们没发现你
I'm surprised they didn't spot you too.
那有一名手上有扑克牌的绝色女子
There's a most remarkable girl back there with a deck of cards.
我上去时看到那些牌都是黑桃
I saw those cards on the way up. Spades, James, every one.
你刚离开74街就被跟踪了
You were nailed the minute you left 74th. There's only one man…
一个人不应该取集这么多黑社会力量在这城里
…who can pull together that much black muscle in town.
他自称是老大
CalIs himseIf Mr. Big.
你说明来意 他们说你欺压黑人
You name the business, they say he has a black concession.
像康乃克那样的国外总理
What would a foreign prime minister like kananga…
为何要跟美国帮派勾结？
…want with an American gangster?
问题是 老大干嘛要和岛屿国家打交道？
The question is, what would Mr. Big want with a two-bit island diplomat?
老大？他怎么会牵涉这案件
Mr. Big? Where the hell does he fit into this mess?
标准菲力的打火机 真耀眼
A genuine Felix lighter. llluminating.
听着 詹姆斯
Listen, James.
我们刚发现康乃克有架私人飞机
we just found out that kananga's got a private plane…
几小时内他就要飞到圣莫利克去
…and he's leaving for San Monique within the hour.
- 帮我安排下一班机好吗？- 我已经安排了
- Then get me on the next flight. - I already did.
我知道你不会错过机会寻求真正的刺激
I knew you wouldn't pass a chance to get away from where the real action is.
各位 传奇性的男爵圣迷迪
The legendary Baron Samedi, folks.
那是沙特蝶 为了说法文的朋友安排的
That's Saturday, for those of you who speak French.
公墓的巫毒教魔鬼和死人部落的酋长
Voodoo God of Cemeteries and Chief of the Legion of the Dead.
以及那位死不了的男人
The Man Who Cannot Die.
但我们的目的 只是为你们这些观众精心安排
But for our purposes, just a performer in a little musical extravaganza…
一场狂想的音乐晚会
…we've cooked up for you wonderful people.
晚安 我叫邦德 有订房
Good evening. The name is Bond. You have a reservation for me.
有的 邦德太太在等你
Yes, Mr. Bond, of course. Mrs. Bond has been expecting you.
- 邦德太太？- 她今天下午到的
- Mrs. Bond? - She arrived earlier this afternoon.
说她比较喜欢隐密点的房间
Said she preferred something a little more private.
12号套？
Bungalow 12.
邦德太太真懂得情调
An incurable romantic, Mrs. Bond.
（塔罗牌）
客房服务
Room service, please.
客房服务？我是邦德先生 12号房
Room service? This is Mr. Bond, bungalow 12.
我要一瓶香槟 微冰就好
I'd like a bottle of Bollinger, please. Slightly chilled.
二个杯子 谢谢
Two glasses. Thank you.
有人在吗？
Anybody home?
先生 你的香槟送来了
Your champagne, sir.
- 什么？- 你的香槟
- What was that? - Your champagne.
放在桌上 谢谢
Put it on the table. Thanks.
- 要我开吗？- 什么？
- Shall I open it? - What?
不 我来 谢谢
No. I can manage. Thank you.
- 这给你 - 谢谢
- There you are. - Thank you.
我猜你是邦德太太？
Mrs. Bond, I presume?
我是罗丝卡佛
I'm Rosie Carver.
我需要解释一下
I guess I have a little explaining to do.
是的 不是你
Yes. Either you or…
就是菲力叔叔
…dear Uncle Felix.
点38口径 史密斯威森
Custom.38 Smith and Wesson.
匣式给弹 没有枪枝标准号码
Corrugated three-inch stock. No serial number.
标准中情局配备
Standard ClA issue.
问题是 为何拿枪指着我？
Question is, why point it at me?
送香槟的人不是旅馆服务生
The man who delivered your champagne is not a hotel waiter.
我只是要小心点
I was just trying to be careful.
关於菲力莱特 你说对了
As for Felix Leiter, you're right.
我在这替中情局工作有段时间了
I've worked for ClA here for some time now.
他打电报说你要来 要求我协助你
He cabled me you were coming and asked if I wouldn't help out.
也许你愿意先从头开始
Perhaps you'd better start by getting your head together.
- 浴室有面镜子 - 是的
- There's a mirror in the bathroom. - Yes.
这只是我第二个任务 知道吗？
You're only my second mission, you know.
我第一个任务是协助被刺杀的班恩
My first was Baines, the agent who was killed.
真庆幸 在你同样协助名单中我是下一个
It's a relief to know I'm next in line for the same kind of aid.
里面有…
There's a…
一条蛇 我忘记告诉你 进去时不要忘记带鼬鼠
A snake. I should have told you. Never go in there without a mongoose.
我早就知道 我不该牵连进来！
I should have never gotten into any of this!
我对你将会是毫无用处的
I'm going to be completely useless to you.
我想你很快会回复正常
I'm sure we'll be able to lick you into shape.
很晚了 邦德太太
It's getting late, Mrs. Bond.
明天我们会很忙
Tomorrow is going to be a very busy day for us.
康乃克在保护
kananga is protecting something down here…
班恩已经发现的
…something which…
某样东西
…Baines obviously discovered.
你要告诉我 班恩尸体在哪找到的
You're going to show me the spot where Baines' body was found.
恐怕只有今晚
That, I'm afraid, only leaves us tonight to…
能重温旧时光
…well, catch up on old times.
菲力告诉我 会发生这种事
Felix told me there'd be moments like this.
老好人菲力怎么说？
What did good old Felix suggest?
若都失败了 还有毒药
If all eIse failed, cyanide pilIs.
我安排了两个卧室
I settled for two bedrooms.
晚安 邦德先生
Good night, Mr. Bond.
邦德太太
Mrs. Bond.
只是一顶帽子 属于一个小头的人
Why, it's just a hat, darling, belonging to a small-headed man…
狭义的说 这个人连一只鸡都斗不过
…of limited means who lost a fight with a chicken.
是警告 把它甩出去！
It's a warning. Get it out of here!
拜托！
Please!
求你今晚别丢下我一个人
Please don't leave me alone tonight.
詹姆斯 答应我
James, please promise me.
好吧 亲爱的 如果你坚持的话
All right, darling, if you insist.
我答应你
I promise.
谢谢你
I thank you.
罗丝！
Rosie!
早餐好了！
Breakfast's up!
（皇后）
- 你好了吗？- 什么？
- Are you ready yet? - What?
我得租辆车
I have to see about organizing a car.
大厅见
I'll see you in the lobby.
（塔罗牌）
来这里 保证一定有大鱼
Over here, sir. Guaranteed big fish.
- 来这里抓大鱼 - 宝贝！
- Catch big fish, sir. - Hey, baby!
过来 带你的男人来 半天只要20元
Over here. Bring your man over here. Just $20. HaIf a day.
你有热情的女士 我们有冰凉的啤酒
You got warm lady. We got cold beer over here.
你要抓大鱼吗？这里只有二磅
You want to catch a big fish? It's only two pounds over here.
早
Good morning.
来 罗丝 这位看起来很积极
Come on, Rosie. This one seems eager enough.
对不起 我能在哪换衣服？
Excuse me. Where can I change?
我 脱衣服 哪里？
Me. Clothes off. Where?
不准动
Stop right there.
慢慢转过来
Turn around slowly.
手举起来！
k eep your hands up!
像我说的 珊瑚 一个差劲探员
As I was saying, Quarrel, a lousy agent…
可是自得其乐
…but the compensations speak for themselves.
罗丝卡佛 见过和我用同一把梳子
Rosie Carver, meet the man who shares my hairbrush…
的珊瑚二世
…Quarrel, Junior.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我差点打死你
I could've shot you.
若你按下保险栓的话 我可能就死了
You might have even killed me if you'd taken off the safety catch.
算了 亲爱的
Never mind, darling.
只要带我们去班恩被杀的地方
You just let us know when we get to the spot where Baines was killed.
就在山坡上 越过下个海湾之后
It's up in the hilIs just after we clear the next cove.
珊瑚 谁住在那儿？
Hey, Quarrel, who the hell lives up there?
康乃克的女人住的房子
That's the house of the kananga woman.
她会邪术
She's supposed to have the power of the Obeah.
除了他没人敢上去
No one on the island dare go up there except him.
他又来了
He comes again.
会有暴乱
There will be violence.
他现在正在接近我们
He approaches even now.
陆路还是水路？
By land or water?
水路
Water.
他已经到达了
He has arrived.
很好 罗丝比我想的还有效率
Good. Rosie's been more efficient than I anticipated.
我知道一个地方能租车
I know a place where we can rustle up a car.
美丽 勇敢 机智
Beautiful, brave, and now resourceful.
罗丝 你展现了后来居上的勇气
Rosie, you seem to be staging a remarkable comeback.
告诉我未来
Tell me about the future.
死亡吗？
Is it death?
我说 是死亡吗？
I said, is it death?
是死亡
It is death.
他们来了
They're coming.
罗丝知道该怎么做
Rosie knows what to do.
这次我不要别人插手 要不留痕迹
Now, I want no bodies this time, no trace.
就在下面
It's down there.
你不是说班恩在山上遇害的
But I thought you said Baines was killed up in the hilIs, darling.
就在那边的山底下
Up in the hilIs down there.
为何我们不吃点午餐同时好好讨论一下？
Why don't we have a bite of lunch and discuss it?
篮子里有很好吃的面饼
There's an excellent patty in the hamper.
我不急
I'm in no hurry.
你呢？
Are you?
不急
No.
你不知道找到你对我的意义
Oh, you don't know what finding you has meant to me.
我想像的到
Oh, I can imagine.
你不知道找到这张牌对我的意义
And you've no idea what finding this has meant to me.
你一定知道上下颠倒的皇后牌的意思吧？
You do know what the Queen of Cups means in an upside-down position?
一个邪恶不忠的女人 一个骗子
A deceitful, perverse woman, a liar, a cheat.
我现在要答案
And I'd like some answers now.
拜托…
Please…
你不了解 如果我说出来 他们会杀了我
You don't understand, see. They'll kill me if I do.
你不说 我也会杀了你
And I'll kill you if you don't.
你不会 也下不了手
But you couldn't. You wouldn't.
做过那件事以后就不会
Not after what we've just done.
我在事前绝不会杀你
I certainly wouldn't have killed you before.
你以前的演技不错 罗丝 现在你差一点了
It used to be a convincing act, Rosie. It's wearing a little thin now.
这不是演戏 这是…
It's not an act. It's…
下定决心
Make your choice.
罗丝！
Rosie.
Rosie!
请解释一下错在哪
You will explain what went wrong.
我看到一个女人的干预
I see the intervention of a woman.
那个女的差点要招供 我们必须要杀她
The girl was about to confess. We had to kill her.
陷阱布置好了
The trap was set.
铁黑在等着
Tee Hee was waiting.
你看见死亡
And you saw death.
一定是那个女人的死亡
It must have been the girI's death.
若你不问详细
If you do not ask specific questions…
我不能为你对答案的误解负责
…I cannot be responsible for your misinterpretation of the answers.
这些不停的乱象 让我心神不宁 索丽塔
These growing signs of impertinence begin to disturb me, Solitaire.
就像你出生前 发生在你母亲身上一样
Even as they did with your mother before you.
她有法力却失去它 对我一点用也没有
She had the power and lost it, became useless to me.
你不会再犯同样的错误
You will not make the same mistake.
邦德现在在哪？
Where is Bond now?
当你用这种态度的时候 我看不到
I cannot see when you are this way with me.
事情变得模糊不清
Things become unclear.
我希望这种偶发消失的法力不会成为习惯
Let us hope these momentary lapses do not become a habit.
你的法力是来服侍我
Your power exists to serve me…
由我来控制
…and it is mine to control.
时间到的时候 我决定你是否失去法力
If and when the time comes I decide you are to lose it…
我自己会收回它
…I myseIf will take it away.
去睡吧 你让我很生气
Solitaire, go to sleep. You have made me angry with you…
而我不想这样
…and I have no wish to be.
铁黑
Tee Hee.
把牌放下！
Put down those cards!
这真是个大不敬！
It is a blasphemy!
对看不懂的人毫无用处
They tell nothing to those who cannot see.
他们的确有其含意 要靠点运气
But they do. That's a bit of luck.
我们都会好运
Good luck for both of us.
牌说我们会成为恋人
The cards say we will be lovers.
你误解它的意思了
You're mistaken.
那是不可能的 禁止我去做…
It's impossible, forbidden for me…
你得离开了
Now you must go.
但你相信
But you do believe…
我是说 真的相信牌
…I mean, really believe in the cards.
它们从来没骗过我
They have never lied to me.
以后也不会
Then they won't now.
挑一张吧
Pick one.
你早知道答案了
You knew the answer before it was given.
真奇怪
Strangely enough, somehow…
我也有同感
…so did l.
终于发生了
So it's finally happened…
就跟我妈的遭遇一样
…just as it did to my mother and…
还有我祖母
…her mother before her.
当然是
Well, of course it did.
你是个活的见证 不是吗？
Well, you're visual proof of that, aren't you?
高兴点
Come on. Cheer up, darling.
每个人都有第一次
Has to be a first time for everyone.
告诉我 康乃克在哪？
Now, tell me, where's kananga?
我看不见
I cannot see.
对了 牌 我帮你拿来
Oh, yes, the cards. I'll get them.
不需要怕
No.
你很快就能摆脱他
There's no need to be frightened.
我保证
You'll soon be rid of him, I promise.
我只是需要点…
I promise.
情报而已
I just need a…
法力
…little bit of information, that's all.
我失去法力了
The power…
最高僧侣
I've lost it.
说过王子的太太 不再控制这个世界
The high priestess is wife to the prince no longer of this world.
通往神秘教堂的精神桥梁
The spiritual bridge to the secret church.
这是我的命运
It's my fate.
为了惩罚我与凡人恋爱
By compelling me to earthly love…
牌已经收回我的法力
…the cards themselves have taken away my powers.
我需要忏悔
Darling, I have a small confession to make.
别感到难过
Now, try not to be too upset.
我只是运气比较好一点
The deck was slightly stacked in my favor.
并没有两样
It makes no difference.
肉体上的亵渎是无法弥补的
The physical violation cannot be undone.
当他发现我失去法力
When he finds out I've lost my power…
他会杀了我
…he'll kill me.
他得先找到你才行
Now, come on. He'll have to find you first.
情侣的第一课… 我们之间没有秘密
Lovers' lesson number one… we have no secrets.
例如说 我有艘船在等
For example, I have a boat waiting.
你可以上船
You can be on it.
在我们离开前 我只要知道
All I have to know before we leave is…
巫毒地后面是什么？
…what goes on back there in Voodooland.
三男一女过去四天内丧命
Darling, three men and a girl have been killed in the last four days…
更别提他们企图阻止我
…not counting the times they've tried to stop me from discovering…
发现康乃克在保护什么
…whatever kananga's protecting.
你要不要上船？
Now, do you want to be on that boat or not?
我只是为他读牌而已
I simply read the cards for him.
我从没去过那儿 他从没带我去过
I've never been there, and he's never taken me there.
我不敢去那里
I've never dared to go…
但我由牌里看出来
…but I've looked in the cards.
那边很丰饶
I've seen great riches there.
他们会杀了你
They'll kill you.
「我们」 亲爱的
"Us, " darling.
他们会杀了我们
They will kill us.
情人守则第二课…
Lovers' lesson number two…
团结一致 只有死亡才能将我们分离
…togetherness till death do us part, or thereabouts.
我们离开前不要留痕迹
Is there time before we leave…
这是第三课？
…for lesson number three?
没错
Absolutely.
没必要穿着衣服上床
There's no sense in going off haIf-cocked.
- 这边走 - 你怎么这么肯定？
- This way. - How can you be so sure?
稻草人只是要吓人 你不怕吧？
These scarecrows are to scare people away. You're not scared, are you?
第四课… 跟随稻草人
Lesson number four… follow the scarecrows.
- 早 老板 - 早
- Good morning, boss. - Good morning.
又是美好的一天
It's sure gonna be a beautiful day.
是的 美好的一天
Yes, sir, a beautiful day.
他们向山顶上走去
They're heading for the hill.
他们来了
They're here.
若他找到的话 杀死他
If he finds it, kill him.
快！
Quick!
我们找不到他们了 他带着那女的
We've lost him. He has the girl.
他们在网子下
They're somewhere under the nets.
不计任何代价
At any cost, any…
邦德一定得死
…Bond must die.
这是25号 我们发现他们了
Unit two-five, we have picked them up.
总部呼叫25号 逮捕邦德
Base to 25. Arrest Bond.
重复 不准碰那女的
But, I repeat, the girl is not to be touched.
收到 了解 完毕
Message received and understood. Over and out.
呼叫所有单位
Base to all units.
重复 不准碰那女的
I repeat, the girl is not to be touched.
- 去拿多点水来 - 别挡住！
- Go get some more water. - Get out of the way!
（矮桥）
我的天啊
Sweet mother of pearl.
终点站 下车了
All change. End of the line.
快到下面去
Get down below quickly.
来 我来 你去发动
Here. I'll do that. You get us started.
好像是突击
It appears a bust.
詹姆斯 他会找我的 我知道他不会罢手
James.
别这样 亲爱的
He'll be looking for me now. I know he'll never stop.
都结束了
Come on, darling.
巫毒地不过是罂栗田而已
It's all over.
单纯的海洛因走私而已
Voodooland was just poppy fields…
我跟菲力联络后 整个案子交给他
…a simple matter of heroin smuggling.
我们就没事了 对了 你想去哪儿？
I'll have a word with a man named Felix and turn the case over to him.
任何一个像现在这样的地方都行
Then you and I will be off. By the way, where would you like to go?
多快能到新奥尔良？
Anywhere where we can find one of these.
再四个小时才到圣塔明那
How quickly can we make it to New Orleans?
你在那搭上飞机 明天一早就到了
Santa Mina, four hours away.
用无线电跟菲力联络
You can catch a flight and be there in the morning.
说明天在皇家东方旅馆见
Then get in touch with Felix on the scrambler.
坦帕比较近
Tell him to meet me there tomorrow. Royal Orleans Hotel.
汉米顿在新奥尔良被害之间一定有关连
Tampa is closer.
我们载的是件相当珍贵的物品
HamiIton was killed in New Orleans, so there has to be a connection.
他ì会想办法夺回去
And this is a valuable piece of merchandise we're carrying…
新奥尔良 国际机场
…which, with any luck, they'll want back.
请到皇家东方旅馆
Royal Orleans Hotel, please.
你确定这是往新奥尔良的路？
Are you sure this is the way to New Orleans?
我不知道 真的难倒哈林来的司机 不是吗？
I don't know, but it sure beats the hell out of Harlem, don't it?
詹姆斯！怎么了 宝贝？
Well, hello, Jim! What's happening, baby?
在后面放轻松点
Just ease back now, Jim. Relax!
老大想见你
Mr. Big wants to see you.
你在岛上犯了个错误
You made a mistake back on that island, Bond.
带走了不属于你的东西
You took something that didn't belong to you…
拿了老大朋友的东西
…and you took it from a friend of Mr. Big's.
那种错误很难弥补
That type of mistake is tough to bounce back from.
- 我才刚刚抵达 - 今天是你的幸运日子
- But I've only just arrived. - Today is your lucky day, Jim.
你要去跳伞
You're going skydiving.
从一万公尺高看那个湖 风景不错
There's a hell of a view of the lake from 10, 000 feet.
我唯一的遗憾是无法亲眼目睹
My only regret is I won't be there to see it.
- 就是他！我们走！- 快！
- Hey, that's him! Let's go! - Come on, come on!
- 早安 你… - 贝尔太大 你不是我的教官？
- Good morning. You're, uh… - Mrs. Bell. You're not my instructor?
- 比利克先生到哪去了？- 不舒服 我来上课
- Where's Mr. Bleeker? - Indisposed. I'll be giving the lesson.
过来！
Come on, come on!
- 今天什么课程？- 我们拭目以待
- What's on for today? - Well, let's just wing it, shall we?
你转速太快
You're over-revving.
里诺 慢点！拜托 慢点！
Leroy, slow down! For Pete's sake, slow down!
- 照那个人说的做！- 我找不到刹车！
- Do what the man say! - I can't find the brake!
关上门！
Close those doors!
糟了！
Holy shit!
小心！
Look out! Look out!
好吧 唐 不用担心 我来处理
Okay, Don. Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
好 我待会再和你谈 我要去上课
Right. Talk to you later. I gotta go and give a lesson.
明天同一时间？
Same time tomorrow, Mrs. Bell?
是的
Yes, Mr. Bleeker. Yes, sir. Well, I know you just…
我知道你不能把翅膀黏回去
…can't glue the wings back on. Now, Mr. Bleeker, I'm sure…
比利克先生 不要生气
…there's no reason for name-calling.
- 今天下午再量其他的 - 是的 先生
- You can fit the rest this afternoon. - Right, sir.
不要忘记开双叉
Don't forget the double vents.
我知道她是你最好的学生
I appreciate she may be… one of your best pupiIs, yes.
很好 有点花俏 我保留其余三条
That'll do nicely. That's a little frantic. I'll keep the other three.
哪种建议能写给华盛顿？
Any suggestion of that kind should be forwarded in writing to Washington.
- 贝尔太大如何？- 在加护病房 她会熬过来
- How is Mrs. Bell? - lntensive care. She'll pull through.
是的 先生 没人怀疑你的爱国情操
Yes, sir. Oh, no, sir, no one's questioning your patriotism.
我肯定你是退役军人
I'm sure you're a veteran, sir.
菲力帮我问一下 是否有间灵魂之最餐厅
Felix, you might find out if there's a Fillet of Soul restaurant in town.
我们比你快一步 在达克街 史特在监视那里
We're way ahead of you. It's on Docker Street. Strutter's watching it now.
（灵魂之最）
好大的场面 这边走
Hell of a send-off. This way.
- 史特在哪？- 一定在里面
- Where's Strutter? - He's gotta be inside somewhere.
先生 二位？
Two, gentlemen?
墙边有好位子
I got a nice booth over here just against the wall.
能不能靠舞台近点的位子？
Do you think you could find something a little closer to the stage?
- 位子有何不好？- 我有一次不好的经验
- What's wrong with a booth? - I once had a nasty turn in a booth.
- 波本酒 不加冰块 - 来两杯
- Bourbon. No ice, please. - Two Sazeracs.
你的冒险家精神到哪去了？这是新奥尔良 放轻松
Where's your sense of adventure, James? This is New Orleans. Relax.
- 有人叫菲力莱特吗？- 是 我就是
- One of you guys called Felix Leiter? - Yeah. Right here.
一位叫史特的人 有电话找你
Telephone call for you. Guy called Strutter.
谢谢 等等 我以为哈瑞弄砸了
Thanks. For a minute there, I thought Harry was laying down on the job.
我的朋友…
What happened to my…
- 我的朋友怎么了？- 你的朋友？
- What happened to my friend? - What happened to your friend?
谢谢你来拜访
Thanks for dropping in, baby.
你这个难搞的家伙
Yeah, you one tough pig to nail down.
你当我是傻子整我
You've been picking at me like some kind of maggot.
首先你到哈林区杀了我们一个兄弟
First you go up to Harlem and kill one of the brothers.
那让我不爽
That disturbed me.
然后你又由我朋友康乃克博士手中
Well, then you go and steal this valuable young lady…
偷走这位珍贵的少妇
…from my good friend, Dr. kananga.
康乃克相信算命那一套 我是说 他气坏了
Now, old kananga, he believes in all that card crap. I mean, he's mad.
持有法律的后盾
Well, possession being nine points of the law…
康乃克现在是你的问题了 谢谢
…I would say kananga is your problem now. Thank you.
事实上 若我是你 我会步步为营
In fact, if I were you, I'd watch my step from now on.
你们就让我自己跟他打交道
Yeah, well, you just let me handle our business with the man.
对你 我有自己的计划
I've got my own plans for you, baby.
但首先
But first…
他要一个小问题的答案
…there's one little question that he wants answers for.
这样你不妨把我送回岛上 让他亲自审问
In that case, you'd better ship me back to the island and let him ask in person.
我不习惯回答多管闲事的人
I'm not in the habit of giving answers to lackeys.
很幸运你还有 留下一个耳朵听问题
You damn lucky you got a ear left to hear the question with…
就是… 你有乱搞吗？
…which is… Did you mess with that?
这是我们三个当事人之间的事 我看见他时自然会跟他说明
That's between Solitaire and myseIf and kananga. I'll tell him when I see him.
除非你回答我 不然你看不见日出！
You won't see the sunlight unless you answer me!
我不知道你这么怕他
I had no idea you were so frightened of him.
- 你有没有碰她？- 当我见到康乃克时
- Did you touch her? - When I see kananga.
好
Right.
真是惊人
Quite revealing.
康乃克是在上千亩良好的伪装用地种植罂栗的人
kananga, poppy grower in thousands of acres of well-camouflaged fields…
而且受到沙特蝶的巫毒教保护
…protected by the voodoo threat of Baron Samedi.
至于老大 透过灵魂之最餐厅连锁店
And as Mr. Big, distributor and wholesaler…
作为大盘商和销售商
…through a chain of Fillet of Soul restaurants.
销售商？
Wholesale?
卖海洛因赚钱？
Sell heroin for money?
抱歉 我确定你只是送给大家
My apologies. I'm sure you simply give it away.
很好 邦德先生
Excellent, Mr. Bond.
那正是我打算执行的计划
That's precisely what I intend to do.
事实上是两吨
Two tons of it to be exact.
当进去一个竞争激烈的场所
When entering into a fiercely competitive field…
给个赠品没什么大不了
…one finds it advisable to give away free samples.
男人 女人 黑人 白人 一律平等
Man or woman, black or white. I don't discriminate.
二吨的海洛因外面市价超过10亿美元
Two tons of heroin with a street value well over a billion dollars…
全国免费分销？
…nationally distributed free?
不会引起某些家族不满？
That should make a certain group of families… …rather angry, wouldn't you say?
不满？
Angry?
为什么？
Why, my dear Mr. Bond…
那逼使他们发疯退出这行业
…it'll drive them out of their minds and, subsequently, out of the business.
真是杰作 福利政策
Quite ingenious. A sort of junkie's weIfare system.
直到这国家吸毒的人
Well, merely until the number of addicts in the country…
提高两倍
…has doubled, shall we say?
我将会开始推销你那天无意闯入的田地
Then I will begin to market that acreage that you blundered into the other day.
海洛因将会十分昂贵 让我和电话公司
That heroin will be very expensive… …leaving myseIf and the phone company…
以后全部垄断
…the only two going monopolies in this nation for years to come.
我以为是索丽塔算的命
And here I thought it was Solitaire did the fortunetelling.
为了你们两人着想 希望她功力还在
Let's hope for both of your sakes she still can.
问题依然存在 由关心人士提出
The question still stands, Mr. Bond, asked by the gentleman concerned.
你有没有碰她？
Did you touch her?
这不是绅士回答的问题
Why, it's not the sort of question a gentleman answers.
前车之鉴
Well, having set the example…
我不相信她还是清白之身
…I don't expect Miss Solitaire to be any less the lady.
对了
By the way…
你的手表好炫
…that's a particularly handsome watch you're wearing, Mr. Bond.
- 能不能借我看？- 抱歉 我起不来了
- May I see it, please? - You'll forgive me if I don't get up.
别用手铐
Butter hook.
铁黑
Tee Hee…
她要是回答错误
…on the first wrong answer from Miss Solitaire…
你就捏邦德先生的右手小指
…you will snip the little finger of Mr. Bond's right hand.
第二次回答错误
Starting with the second wrong answer…
找更重要的部位
…you'll proceed to the more vital areas.
亲爱的
Solitaire, my dear…
你仔细听好
…I want you to listen to me very carefully.
邦德先生手表后面登记的号码
On the back of Mr. Bond's watch, the registration number…
…3-2-6-6
…3-2-6-6.
正确吗？
Do I speak the truth?
是的
You speak the truth.
很好
Well.
若没别的事 你暂时不需要怕了
If nothing eIse, at least I have laid your fears to rest.
我恭贺你这么精密的计划
My compliments on a splendid operation.
不过还有一件事
There is one thing, however, the…
带他去农场
Whisper, take him to the farm.
我们什么时候回去？
When do we start back?
很快
Soon, Solitaire, soon.
为什么？
Solitaire, why?
我对你这么好 你什么都有
I treated you well. You lacked for nothing.
- 我不了解你说… - 邦德先生的手表
- I don't understand what you… - Mr. Bond's watch, my dear.
我给你我最大的宽容 你有5成的机会
I gave you every break possible. You had a 50-50 chance.
你根本就不对
You weren't even close.
我别无选择
I had no choice.
请相信我 这些牌
Please believe me. The cards.
时机成熟时 我会给你想要的
When the time came, I myseIf would have given you love.
你知道的！
You knew that. You knew that!
处理这件事只有一个办法
There's only one proper way to deal with this.
（死亡）
时机成熟时
And one proper time.
（入侵者会被吃掉）
实验快要成功了
The tonnage order is nearly complete.
我们今晚动身
We move it out tonight.
我说今晚
And I mean tonight.
邦德先生
Mr. Bond.
你对鳄鱼了解多少？
How much do you know about crocodiles, Bond?
我始终跟他们保持距离
Oh, I've always tried to keep them at arm's length, myseIf.
他们很可爱 不是吗？
Cute little nippers, ain't they?
我不相信这些将来有可能变成皮包的是孤儿
I don't suppose those potential overnight bags are orphans?
不 我们还有爸爸妈妈
Oh, no. We have some moms and dads as well.
事实上 有好几千只
In fact, quite a few thousand.
这是我最喜欢的部份 喂食时间到了
This is the part I like best, feeding time.
我想那是全程的最高峰
I suspect the highlight of the tour.
有些宝贝活了200年
Some of these babies live to be 200 years old.
看那边那一条
Look over there.
那是鳄鱼 从圆鼻子能看得出来
That's an alligator. You can always tell by its round nose.
这是老艾柏！
Aha! There's old Albert.
他是条鳄鱼
Now, he's a croc.
有一次不小心 它咬掉我整只手臂
Got overcareless with him sometime back and he took my whole arm off.
- 干得好 艾柏！- 它们什么都吃 甚至同类
- Well done, Albert. - They'll eat anything, even each other.
有时候 它们整年不吃东西
Then again, sometime they can go a whole year without eating.
- 我宁愿等那一刻 - 有两种方法
- Oh, I was rather counting on that. - There are two ways…
不让鳄鱼伤人
…to disable a crocodile, you know.
我相信你不会跟我分享这种消息？
I don't suppose you care to share that information with me?
一个办法是拿笔戳它的双眼
One way is to take a pencil and jam it in the depression hold behind his eyes.
另一个呢？
And the other?
另一个更简单
Oh, the other is twice as simple.
你只要把手放在它嘴里
You just put your hand in his mouth…
把它的牙齿拔出来
…and pull his teeth out.
失火了！
It's on fire!
亚当 抓住他！
Adam, get him!
用车阻止他！快！
Adam, get the car! Cut him off! Hector, move, damn it!
邦德抢走一艘船 驶往爱雨兰滩头
Bond ripped off one of our boats! He's headed for the lrish Bayou.
抓到他的人才能活
The man that gets him stays alive.
快去！
Now, move, you mother…
（欢迎到路易斯安那）
托比！
Toby!
发现超速驾驶
Toby, I got me a regular Ben Hur down here…
时速95英里
…doing 95 minimum.
- 需要人手帮忙吗？- 不需要！
- Need any help, J.W.? - Hell, no!
你有一辆会超速的车子
You got a set of wheeIs that just won't quit, boy…
如果是你的车的话
…if they's yours, that is.
转过去 小子 双手放在车头盖上
You spin around, boy. Ten fingers on the fender.
腿分开
Legs apart.
我想你今天运气不好
I'm sure this ain't exactly your debut with this sort of thing.
挑错道路开快车
You picked the wrong parish to haul ass through, boy.
没人能逃得过比柏警长的追踪
Nobody cuts and runs on Sheriff J.W. Pepper…
现在是他在说话
…and it's him speaking now, by the by.
搞什么…
What the fu…
你处理完那辆违规车之后
J.W., soon as you nail that offending vehicle…
泰森小姐打来
…Miss Pearson just called.
她的狗口吐白沫
Seems her dog's foaming all at the mouth.
她把它关在木屋里
She's got him locked up in the shed…
问你是否愿意过去找她 杀了那条徇
…wondering if you'd like to come over and shoot it for her.
告诉泰森小姐 去做梦吧
You tell Miss Pearson take a flying Dog.
看来有一艘船卡在警长的车子
That look like a boat stuck in the sheriff's car there, Eddie?
你这辈子到哪去了？那是最新型的车船
Boy, where you been all your life? That there's one of them new car-boats.
这个警区
By the powers invested in me…
赋予我的权力
…by this parish…
我命令此辆车子
…I hereby do commandeer this vehicle…
和里面所有的人
…and all those persons within.
就是你们两位 痞子
And that means you, smart-ass.
23号就位
Unit 23 in position.
请回答 23号呼叫28号
Ten-four, 23. Come in, 28.
好像迪克罗杰
Hey, J.W., seems like Deke Rogers…
他的船在岸边被偷了
…done got his boat stole off the river…
但在他游泳池找到一艘新船
…but picked up a new one in his swimming pool.
警长 你要我让你的人不要听这个频道吗？
Sheriff, you want to get your boys off our frequency?
给我！听我说！
Give me that! Now you listen to me, trooper boy!
我们有群黑小子
We got a swamp full of black Russians…
意图扰乱治安！
…driving boats to beat the band down here!
放轻松 警长 我们在术勒桥处安排了路障
Relax, Sheriff. We've got a roadblock waiting for them at Miller's Bridge.
26号车在米勒桥 我们就快准备好了
Unit 26 at Miller's Bridge. We're just about all set here.
要确定那边百密不疏 听到吗？
Make that secure there, you hear?
各位 他们来了
Okay, fellas, here they come.
让开！我负责这里！
All right, out of my way! I'm in charge here!
你们两位 快点！
You two boys, come on!
我不要听理由 我要那两个人和他们的船
I don't want excuses. I want those two men and their boats…
- 立刻被逮捕 - 是 队长
- apprehended immediately, did you hear? - Yes, sir, Captain.
我了解 但我不知道
I understand. But I don't know right off…
哪可以找比他们还快的船
…where we'll find a boat fast enough to catch them.
我有主意了 你通知我姊夫 比利包德
I got it. You call my brother-in-law Billy Bob.
他有最快的飞艇！
He got the fastest boat on the whole damn river!
他会修理他们 不是吗？打给他
Billy Bob will sure enough fix their ass, huh? Yeah, call Billy Bob.
（州立野生动物部门 牧场站1号）
比利包德 有两艘船开得很快
Now, there's two boats, Billy Bob, and they're moving like buttered pigs.
我向他们保证 你抓得到他们
Now, I promised these boys here you would get them.
- 别让我失望 知道吗？- 冷静点 我就来了
- Don't let me down, hear? - Cool down, J.W. I'm on my way.
- 你要什么吗？- 我想借船
- You want something, boy? - I'd like to borrow this boat, if I may.
整条河的人都想借船
Everybody on the river would like to borrow this boat.
我们发现他们了
Billy Bob, we got them spotted.
他朝哈利的地方
They're headed for Haley's Landing.
那是我姊夫比利包德！
That's my brother-in-law! That's Billy Bob!
他会逮住他们
He'll get them. Billy Bob'll get them.
该死！
Hot damn!
如果包德家族之一逮不住他们 其他家族会逮住他们
If one side of the Pepper family don't get them, the other side will.
我们走！
Let's go!
任何人能找出正当理由
If any man can show just cause…
他们不能现在结婚
…why they may not lawfully be joined together…
请说出来 否则此后永远…
…let him now speak, or eIse hereafter and forever…
总部通知各单位
Headquarters to all units, suspects seen…
嫌犯通过自由角朝11号公路
…proceeding down via Liberty towards Highway 11.
谨慎接近
Proceed with caution.
把那辆破车离开道路 好吗？
Would you get that chicken coop off the road?
你有没有想申请一张驾照？
Did you ever think of getting a driver's license, boy?
你确定他是你姊夫？
Are you sure that was your brother-in-law, Sheriff?
（让乘船成为有趣的娱乐 时速3英里）
- 菲力 你在这干嘛？- 等下再告诉你
- Hello, Felix. What are you doing here? - We'll get to that later.
康乃克带着你的女友在城里 他们刚离开
kananga's in town. He's got your girl with him. They just took off.
这个王八！我抓住他们了！
There's the son of a bitch! I got him!
你是谁？
What are you?
末日机器吗？
Some kind of doomsday machine, boy?
我们监牢可以关得住你这种人
Well, we got a cage strong enough to hold an animal like you here.
- 请你向警长说明 好么？- 是
- Would you enlighten the sheriff? - Yes, sir.
JW让我跟你私下谈谈
J.W., let me have a word with you.
JW这位仁兄从英国来
J.W., now, this fella's from London, England.
他是名英国人 和我们工作人员合作…
He's an Englishman working in cooperation with our boys…
好像是秘密情报员
A sort of secret agent.
秘密情报员？
Secret agent?
帮谁的？
On whose side?
我们一小时前搜查了灵魂之最酒店
We busted the Fillet of Soul an hour ago.
就只找到这些
We came up with nothing but these.
没逮捕到康乃克 你应该见见…
kananga's clear. You should have seen…
和他一起上船那个家伙的体型
…the size of the guy who got on the boat with him.
我发誓有9尺高
Nine feet tall, I swear.
大宽帽 一手拿著可笑的笛子 另一手抓著索丽塔
Big top hat, a cockamamie flute in one hand and Solitaire in the other.
（月亮 死亡）
燃烧炸弹定在午夜爆炸
The incendiary bombs are set for midnight.
刚好给你三十分钟
Now, that gives you exactly 30 minutes.
回来时小心鲨鱼
Watch out for sharks on the way back.
- 早餐见 菲力 - 狩猎愉快
- I'll see you for breakfast, Felix. - Good hunting.
你回来时会需要这个 还有鲨鱼枪
You're going to need these and the shark gun on the way back.
- 派对好像开始了 - 替我向沙特蝶男爵问好…
- Seems like the party's started. - My regards to Baron Samedi…
就在两眼之问
…right between the eyes.
出问题了！
Trouble!
邦德先生 你来了！索丽塔小姐也来了
Ah, Mr. Bond, there you are! And Miss Solitaire, as well.
虽然是不速之客 仍然欢迎
Hardly unexpected, but most welcome.
惠士勃！
Whisper!
再拿两个玻璃杯给我们的贵宾！
Two more glasses for our guests!
- 我们为何而喝？- 地震如何？
- What shall we drink to, Mr. Bond? - Well, how about an earthquake?
- 欢迎回家！我们的那小子呢？- 随时会回来
- Welcome home! Where's our boy? - He'll be along anytime now.
我检查过石头底下 他的潜水衣不见了
I checked behind a rock, and his wet suit is gone.
零钱不用找了
k eep the change.
很不幸的 你的潜水衣
It's unfortunate that your wet suit was discovered…
在田地被摧毁前找到了
…only minutes before the field was destroyed.
- 别说你没保险 - 没有 罂栗花是很娇贵的花朵
- Don't tell me you're not insured. - No. The poppy's a very sturdy flower.
你一直都是捣蛋鬼
You have been a relatively minor nuisance, in fact.
这把枪…
But this gun…
我发现它特别吸引人 是什么？
I find it particularly fascinating. What is it?
鲨鱼枪 一把气枪
A shark gun, naturally, with compressed gas pellets.
天才之作！
lngenious!
别把针拉出来
Don't pull the pin out.
这里的空气已经够臭了
The air in here is foul enough already.
想不到你还是输不起的输家
Aw! Somehow I never thought of you as a poor loser.
我本来希望和你一起敬未来
I was hoping you would join me to a drink to the future.
索丽塔小姐以前都知道未来
Miss Solitaire used to know all about the future.
她对预测死亡特别拿手
She was especially good at predicting death.
一条地下铁路
An underground monorail.
和你最后的老巢相接
Connected to the last refuge of a scoundrel, no doubt.
我想海洛因是从这里由绞车运走
The heroin leaves here, I take it, carried somewhere by that winch.
没错 邦德先生 你学得很快
Correct again, Mr. Bond. What a quick study you are.
让我示范究竟是怎么启动的
Let me show you exactly how it works.
- 那位仁兄到底去哪儿？- 放轻松
- Where in hell can the man be? - Relax.
一定有事耽误了
He must have got tied up somewhere.
每个箱子载重25磅
These cans hold 25 pounds each.
一共要运20箱 由水路运行
There are 20 cans to a shipment, packed in watertight…
金属装置
…metal containers.
少夸张了 我想有更快淹死人的方法
It's your show, but I'm sure there must be a simpler way of drowning someone.
淹死 我不相信你有机会被淹死
Drown, Mr. Bond? I doubt you'll get the chance to drown.
也许可以试简单的方法
Perhaps we could try something in an even simpler vein.
相反的 邦德先生
On the contrary, Mr. Bond.
这些伤口很要命
I think you'll find those wounds quite fatal.
惠士勃
Whisper.
大门
The gate.
慢点 惠士勃！
Oh, slowly, Whisper! Slowly, slowly.
集合用餐者
Let our diners assemble.
小心！
Look out!
- 康乃克到哪去 - 他总有一套…
- Where's kananga? - Well, he always did have…
自我膨胀的方法
…an inflated opinion of himseIf.
詹姆斯
Oh, James.
我们怎么出去？
How do we get out of here?
当然是搭火车
We take the train, of course.
谢谢你今晚做的一切
Thanks for everything, Felix. I'll see you tomorrow night…
明天晚上九点在21俱乐部见 别迟到了
Thanks for everything, Felix. I'll see you tomorrow night at the 21 Club. Don't be late.
我仍看不出来你为何要这样旅行
I don't see why you'll travel this way.
你们在火车上16小时可以做什么？
I mean, what the hell can the two of you do on the train for 16 hours?
向菲力说再见
Say good-bye to Felix, darling.
玩「吉拉密」首先是
Now, the first thing to learn in playing gin rummy is to never take…
除非你正需要
…a card from the exposed pile.
别拿摊在桌上的牌
unless you really need it.
胡了！
Gin.
你在干嘛？
James, what are you doing?
只是想证实一个老传说
Just testing an old adage.
不幸运的一对牌…
Unlucky at cards…
- 快点 詹姆斯 - 马上就好
- Do hurry up, James. - Won't be a moment, darling.
上床前别忘记锁门
Lock the door as well on your way up, would you, James?
总而言之 你不会想别人闯进来 对吗？
After all, we wouldn't want anyone to just walk in on us, would we?
第一次我感觉像个完整的女人
The first time in my life, I feel like a complete woman.
和你的手轻微接触…
The slightest touch of your hand…
我怕我们分手 会唤起过去不如意
I was always so afraid that a part of me would stay with the past…
但现在 我知道不可能发生
…but now I know there's no chance of that any longer.
伸出去接触你
Just to be able to reach out and touch you.
邦德先生 真高兴再见到你
Mr. Bond, it's good to see you again.
詹姆斯！
James!
怎么回事？让我出去！
What's going on? Let me out of here!
詹姆斯 放我出去！
James, let me go!
这不好笑！
Well, that wasn't very funny.
你要干嘛？
Now what are you doing?
只是解除武装
Just being disarming, darling.